http://www.ajay-sqm.com/privacy-policy/

Effective Date:  May 24, 2018
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Ajay-SQM Group and our website; https://www.ajay-sqm.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:
What information we collect;
With whom it is shared;
How it can be corrected;
How it is secured;
How policy changes will be communicated; and
How to address concerns over misuse of personal data.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email, completion of forms on our website, or other direct contact information from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.We will not contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via e-mail at: privacy@ajay-sqm.com or by calling us at 770-943-6202 :
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data
Forms
We request information from you on our Quote Request & Whistleblower forms on our website. This information is solely used to respond to your inquiry.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g. sales, customer service, or compliance department employees) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Cookies
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites (LinkedIn). Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Notification of Changes
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to make changes or updates, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and other places we deem appropriate.
Contact Us
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 770-943-6202 or via email: privacy@sales-ajay.com. We will respond to all requests, inquiries or concerns in a timely manner.
latest news
- Our Relationship With SQM
- News: Organic Dairy Industry Makes Iodine Discovery
- Featured Product: ETPPI
Featured Stories
Home
Company
Resources
Our Commitment
The company's goal is simple: to give valued customers peace of mind that the iodine products on which they bank the success of their companies have been given the utmost care and attention. Read more about our commitment to our products, our customers, and our environment here.
The IODEAL products for your iodine needs from:
Privacy Policy |
Whistleblower Policy
Ajay-SQM Group | Iodeal Brands | © Copyright 2018 All Rights Reserved
